Hello,
Ethan. What's up man?
Just me. Happy New Year.
Happy New Year to you too.
How's it going? It's been a, it's been a while.
Has been a while. Yeah. It's, it is going pretty good.
I've, um, I remember since the last call we spoke about,
um, structuring your day.
Yeah. How's that been? And
Yeah, it's been, it's been really good.
I took, I took some notes in that, um, meeting
and a lot of the things you said I've been trying
out and they've been really helping.
So, uh, I've, you know, you said about going
for a walk in the morning and having consistent wake up
times and like a consistent daily routine,
um, that's been really helping.
And I've been going, instead
of just staying in my room all day for work, I've been going
to other places, like coffee shops, things like that.
So it's like, that's for work.
And then home is more for home if that makes the,
like, uh, separating the relaxing
and work spaces, if that makes sense.
That's awesome. Yeah.
There's something about you look healthier,
like I feel like you, you maybe look happier,
you look lighter, like your energy's lighter.
Um, so That's amazing, man. I'm super happy to hear that.
Um, it's like, it's like the simple things.
It's the basics, you know, but we tend to overlook that
and just grind, grind, grind.
Um, and then we end up burning out.
I just had this conversation with, uh, with Sparse,
and he was, he was hitting kind of a roadblock
with his energy and his inspiration.
And it, it came down
to sometimes we set these like really unrealistic
expectations on ourselves
and what we're, what we have
to accomplish in a certain amount of time.
And if we don't, if we don't achieve that, then, you know,
we get down on ourselves.
We feel like we're not making any progress.
Um, is that, is that Venom? No, that's a bad guy.
Oh, it looks like Venom. Good job, bud. I, and yeah.
And so a lot of that is just, Hey man, it's like
the routine is everything.
Um, tell me more about like, what you're doing.
So like, are you sleeping better now?
Mm-Hmm. Yeah. A loads better.
I've been, um, trying to change a lot of my, like,
routines and health things to try to be more natural
and like holistic health, if that makes sense.
Yeah. And I, I definitely, so since I've been going out
to do work, I, I've just mentally I feel a lot, a lot better
and yeah, like, like I said, consistent wakeup times
and I just, I just feel a lot, a lot happier.
I love that. Yeah.
I've been, I've been doing other things.
Well, it, it is just taking my health, just trying
to be a bit more healthy.
Yeah. Without a doubt.
That's, um, how is the business?
How is that affecting the business?
It is, it is doing really well. It is, it is.
That's helping me a lot
because I feel like tasks aren't as difficult anymore.
Uh, I feel just like everything is, I'm
so excited to do everything.
Aw. Um, I, I dunno what you,
you said when you were younger, you had that just kind
of constant energy and fire.
Mm-Hmm. And also a big thing I've,
I've been doing recently is cutting out all the negativity.
Mm-Hmm. So negative people and,
and negative words of, and ways of thinking.
I've just been cutting that out completely and help me.
I love that so much, man.
It's so, you don't realize all this,
call it like clogs
and like, it's like a, it's like a, it's like a pipe,
it's like a sewage line
and it's just filled with gunk, you know, from your habits
to your food, to your poor sleep, to the words you use to
how you talk to yourself.
How do you talk to others who you allow into your circle.
All of that is either draining your energy
or it's adding you adding to your energy.
And we're, I would say like most,
most people are completely unaware of, of the things
that are draining us of energy because it takes awareness
and it takes discipline
and it takes almost like facing the facts,
like facing yourself of like, Hey, this isn't working.
Like something needs to change. Right.
Versus just like staying in it
and just kind of like, moving through life.
Like, like you're in mud.
Like it feels like you're just like,
you have all this weight on you, this unnecessary weight.
And once you release that, it's like you said, you're,
you're just gliding, you're flowing through the day.
Um, I love that you brought up the whole like
negative negativity aspect of things.
Um, tell me more about that.
'cause I, I'm, I'm a big, like,
I'm big on on that aspect too.
So
With my business I had the main,
my main business partner Finn I've told you about.
Mm-Hmm. And was someone else called Roman.
Um, he wasn't, he's not really a business partner.
We just kind of brought him in as well.
It is mainly been me and Finn.
And so in the daytime, well we used to,
because he's not, this isn't very nice,
but he is not as, um, like creative
and, uh, proactive in his thinking.
Mm-Hmm. And he is quite lazy.
And so me, Finn
and this other person's called Roman would
all collaborate together on things.
And what would happen was would say things to the group
and the group wouldn't respond back.
But when I was with Finn talking one-on-one,
we'd always collaborate and do things much more quicker
and and efficiently.
So we've kind of been just not speaking to Roman as much.
'cause he is always like, quite down and quite sad
and quite lazy.
Mm-Hmm. And it seems to have helped a lot.
And the ideas have just been flowing
and been a lot more productive.
And I, I know it's, it's not great to get rid of people.
I, I, I don't, we spoke about that a few weeks ago,
well, a few months ago.
And, but I think it is definitely important if the,
like a chain is only as strong as the weakest link.
Correct. So we've been removing that
and it seems to have been helping.
But I, I, I think in business you have
to be ruthless, don't you?
And just look at things from how it is rather than, oh,
he's our friend and Mm-Hmm.
Yeah. That's the hardest part.
It's, and I actually love that metaphor.
'cause it, it makes, it's like absolutely correct.
Um, of you, you are the, the weakest,
like you are only as strong as your weakest link.
Yeah. And when I had a big team, I had a lot of weak,
I had a few weak links that was bringing down the whole ship
and, and they were like such a important part of the process
of like, the whole production.
And if like, if they did wrong,
the whole production would be off.
It would, like, for example, they were script writers
and like, if, if they just didn't understand the angle
and stuff like that, like the videographers
and the production people would shoot all of that.
The, they would, the finished product
would be completely off.
And it's like, you waste all this time and energy.
And it's like, that's just one thing.
Like there was another employee that I had who was very,
like, very opinionated
and very, like, he was very insecure.
So like, if he had any, uh, critiques
or criticism, he would take it personally
and then made this big deal about like, everybody,
it was just like such a nightmare.
Even though he was really good at his job, he had like,
personal and security issues.
And the Yeah.
When it comes down to business, it's a very, like,
it is facing the truth, like with objectivity as, and,
and I've had to learn this lesson so many times.
It's like, you gotta let people go
who aren't bringing you forward, uh,
who keep making mistakes,
who are bringing negative energy to the group.
And you can feel it, man.
Um, you know, a business should, you know,
it's not always gonna be, but like harmonious.
Like things should be in harmony.
Like with your business partner,
with your employees, with your clients.
When you're noticing these things like disharmony,
it's like, should I cut this client?
Should I let go of this person? Should I replace them?
'cause it, ultimately, you are in control
of your business, right?
When you keep these things on, you're like allowing them
to control your business and control you
and control how you feel.
It's, it's like one of those things that you have to learn
to like, stand up for yourself
or take pride in like what you do and like, take ownership.
I don't know how many times I've had to like, let people go
and it's like always the worst type of conversation,
but it's always the best like, feeling afterwards.
Um, it's, yeah.
It, it sucks, especially when you have a, a,
a relationship with them.
Um, it's, it's just part of the consequences
of getting into business with people that, you know,
that you like personally have a friendship with.
Then, you know, you kind of risk this.
I may not be friends with you afterwards if
that's just nature, man.
That's just the way it is. But yeah.
Have you, are you guys gonna go to that point?
Yeah. I, I think so.
That, that, that is the plan with him.
But it, it's, it is a shame because, and also me
and, um, Finn are quite similar on, on a lot
of different levels, and we've been trying to help Roman,
um, but he is not really been, he's, uh, there's a phrase
that people like helping people who help themselves
and Roman isn't really helping himself.
So at the moment, he's,
he's a full-time video editor for us.
Oh, he is. And Yeah.
And he has just been really, really slow.
So over three days, he produced three
about a minute long videos.
Mm-Hmm. And that's, and,
and he, the worst thing is, is he's, he lies about it too.
So he claims to, to be working, like waking up at six
and he's working 16 hours a day,
but then the, the results don't show that.
And, and there's a lot of things as well.
He is really not very proactive.
So, um, Finn followed up with him and also me
and Finn are spending almost all of our energy kind of
bringing him up and helping him.
'cause he keeps making mistakes. Yeah.
He, and he, when we followed up asking,
how are you getting on with these videos?
He, he then said, oh, I can't do them
because there's a problem with access to the footage.
And we just assumed that he he was working on them. Yeah.
And he didn't say anything.
He just didn't do them even though we were expecting them.
Yeah. And then there's also a few other things he was
managing, like other editors,
and we had to stop him from doing that
because he kept making those mistakes.
Yeah. And it was simple things like, um,
like we were using Asana and
whenever we had a task, he'd like update all the rows,
like which editor's doing it?
When's the start date, the,
the sale value things, things like that.
Mm-Hmm. And he wouldn't do it at all.
So me and Finn would go to look on the progress of a task
and it would just be all, we've got no idea what's going on.
Mm. And another thing as well, when
I was editing videos, I always tried to
organize like my naming conventions within
the editing software.
And he just names them like video one
and Video two E even though,
but we, um, have this naming convention SOP Yeah.
That we seem to follow. And he is just not following it.
And I don't think he's taking it seriously. Yeah.
If, if that makes sense.
So, and I, he has been bringing us down
and since we've been away from him, he's,
we've really quite picked up.
But I do, I do feel a bit, um, bad because he's a friend.
Yeah. Well, it sounds like he's not ready
to take on the responsibility that you're giving him.
Um, you know, excuses, like, anytime you come across someone
who has a ton of excuses,
and I've seen it all, um, it means
that this person isn't like taking full responsibility
for themselves, um, for their mistakes.
And they're not coming up with solutions to prevent it.
It's easy to blame, so easy to blame
external things, da da, da.
Like, you know, I, it, it, it, it's like owning up
to your mistakes is one of the hardest things to do
because like, your ego doesn't want to,
but if you can find someone who makes a mistake
and then owns up to it
and then says, his is what I'm gonna do
because of that mistake,
then you found someone who's worth keeping.
People makes mistakes. You can forgive mistakes.
But, um, finding solution oriented people who are like,
you don't keep running to the same
issue with over and over again.
I had to cut, I had
to cut an editor last year because of that.
I'm like, dude, you're not, you're not improving.
Like, keep reminding you the same thing.
And I've given, I hate giving people multiple chances.
Um, I've given give a lot of 'em a chances.
I'm a nice person, but, you know, I, I expect
a certain level of quality
and I expect a certain level of dedication from everyone.
You know? 'cause like, that's just what it is.
Like, if you hold a high standard for yourself, you know,
you expect others to hold the same standard.
And so if someone does not meaning your standard,
then they're probably not a good fit.
And these are like Yeah.
Massively hit the nail on the head. Exactly. That.
But that's exactly it.
We, we kept telling him, we kept telling him things
and he wasn't listening, he wasn't improving.
And the solution oriented person,
like you just said, they've got a problem.
And they say, yeah, that's my mistake.
I've got a problem on this is how I'm gonna fix it.
That's exactly what me and Finn are like. Mm-Hmm.
And Rodan does not do that. He has a problem.
And then just he, he doesn't do anything about it.
But yeah, that's, I I also, uh, apart of kind of a new,
some changes I've been doing is looking at
opportunity cost a bit more.
Mm-Hmm. Like this, this sounds a little bit stupid,
but this is kind of the analogy.
Like today I was at the coffee shop
and I don't like wasting loads of money,
but I thought buying a coffee
because of the caffeine kind of gives you a bit more focus.
Mm-Hmm. By me going to coffee shops to work it, it
by me being more productive, even though it takes a bit
of time to get there and stuff, it,
that's gonna bring more value than just working at home.
That's one of the things I really like about a business
every single daily, uh, thing
that you do can have quite a big impact on,
on your business and outcome.
Yes. Absolutely. And sparse, are you there right now?
I know you're in the chat.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm here.
I'm just a little lost on the context, but
Oh, sorry.
Yeah. I think, no, I think this is actually really
relevant to you right now.
Um, 'cause Ethan, when we first jumped on the call,
he was telling me how the last call we jumped on
and we spoke about routines and, and sleeping
and, you know, taking care
of yourself, creating time for yourself.
Yeah. He's been applying it
and he's seen incredible results in his overall Mm-Hmm.
Productivity, clarity, happiness.
Um, and one of the things that he,
we just like we picked up on was, you know,
him cutting out negativity.
And one of those negative people was one
of his like employees or partners.
And that's kind of where we're talking about like, you know,
the standards and stuff
and how, you know,
there's certain pro certain people don't take accountability
and responsibility for their actions,
then they're not like Yeah.
A good fit. But I think this goes hand in hand with, with
where what you're, what you're going through with Ethan,
you taking the time to go to a coffee shop, for example,
even though it does cost you more time,
the intrinsic value of you feeling
like better about yourself, that you're somewhere else.
Yeah. You know, external location, you're in an environment
where there's life and there's people and you have caffeine.
Yes. You'll be more productive because you're happier.
Right? Yeah. It doesn't,
it's not quantitative at that point.
It's qualitative. It's like the quality
of your work is gonna be improving.
Like, it doesn't matter how much time
it takes to get something done.
Like I can get the same amount of work done in an hour,
or I can choose to spend three hours on it.
It's like, I'd rather spend an hour on it.
If I'm an hour, if I take an hour to do it
and I'm super stoked, it's because I'm very happy.
Right. So, right.
But you can spend three hours just like, ugh,
dragging your feet doing something, you know?
Yeah. Because you're not, like, you're not happy doing it.
You don't want to do it. Um, so yeah.
You are, you're talking about opportunity costs, right?
So like how has that, are there other things
that you've kind of deemed as opportunity costs
or is that, would you consider that an opportunity cost
or is that like a benefit?
Like going to a coffee shop? Yeah.
Oh, sorry, you just cut out for a minute there.
Um, uh, opportunity.
I, I would say it, it brought me quite a lot.
'cause also the, the one I go to with, there's a lot
of people working there as well.
It's not just everyone sit back and relax.
There's loads of people on their laptops working
and that kind of, you know,
how humans are like social animals and, and a group.
Yeah. That kind of accountability.
If everyone's around working Mm-Hmm.
Then I can't just sit back, relax, and go on my phone
because everyone's working.
Yeah. And,
and also I've been, I've been doing a, a few things,
like I've been going to the sauna a lot
'cause I know the sauna's good for you.
And it, and I find that really, I have a lot
of tangible benefits from that, like, with my focus and,
and how happy I feel.
Mm-Hmm. Um,
and also I had a bit of problems,
this is kind of mentally as well.
I had a few problems with my skin, like spots and, and that,
and the sa the sauna's been helping clear that up.
And that's been having like a knock on effect
to making me feel happier and,
and better about myself. Yeah.
Makes sense. Totally. I think the,
the main thing here is like Ethan has basically like,
has been creating time for himself.
Yeah. And I think, like I was mentioning you earlier,
sparse, it's like, man, like
we all gotta f*****g prioritize ourselves.
You know, prioritize our own joy, our own health,
our own happiness
before we give it away somewhere else, you know,
before we like give it to somebody, like a new project or,
or you, you, the analogy is like, your cup has
to be filled if you want to give it to somebody else.
Like if you wanna share it. Yeah.
You can't share an empty cup.
Um, and you fill it up that way. Um, yeah.
I think that's awesome. Sparse.
Is there anything right, right now that like you
are thinking about doing after we had our morning call, like
Oh yeah. Travel number
one.
Yeah, Absolutely. Yeah.
And just to trying to be on a more, like,
I, I, I know it helps for me that to organize myself better
and, uh, as we talk they doing not a lot of things,
but little things, but doing it consistently
over a longer period of time.
Mm-Hmm. So organizing my week like this,
maybe I'm gonna do the same chat GPT thing you did.
And yeah, I think this,
and just giving myself some more time.
Uh, and I really resonate
with the cup analogy.
And also, uh, when you said that, oh, you
sometimes you're just not happy
and that's when you are kinda like, oh, sitting there
and being like, oh, I don't want to do this
because you're not happy and when you are you,
you have much more quality work done.
So Yeah. Really resonate with this as well.
Totally. Totally. Man.
Even if I'm not happy,
like I don't produce good quality work if I do it.
Like Yeah. Just doing it. I'm not like,
Exactly. Not like it's the same for me,
I think. Yeah. You're not channeling
better inspiration. Like Yeah.
Do you guys understand like frequency and vibration at all?
Do you understand that? Yeah, I think. Okay. Yeah.
So like when you're at a high frequency,
you're vibrating high,
like you're accessing way more intuition
and ver versus like, if you're at a low level depression,
anger, resentment, annoyance, any
of these emotions, you're attracting that.
Right. You're keeping yourself low. Yeah. Low vibration.
And the whole goal for me in the morning is
to raise my frequency, um, before I do anything.
And so the meditation, I just started doing,
um, what's it called?
Um, Wim Hof Breathing. You ever heard of that? Yeah.
It's like, it's his technique. Wim Hof.
He's just a crazy guy who like swims in like the Arctic
and just a crazy guy.
Like very, yeah. Impressive.
But like, basically, you know,
after I do my, my 15 me minute meditation, I'm super clear,
very centered, and then I go into this breathing technique
and it kind of like wakes me up
and it also kind of clears more anxiety.
So, you know, if I don't do that,
it's almost like I go into my day like being pooled in
50 million directions without having a strong center.
Yeah. And base. And if you ever, you ever see everyone knows
what that feels like, being very reactive.
Like you're like quick to snap Yeah.
Quick to like, get angry, quick to like, you know,
respond versus like taking time to like pause and think
and then decide.
And I believe that meditation
and all those things are like, taking your time, like going
to the sun or walking allows you to create a, a gap,
a buffer between you and the stimuli.
So it's like, yeah.
When you don't do it, you're like, you're like,
you just hit the stimuli
and it's like anxiety, it's depression, what the f**k?
But when you have this buffer, it's like, oh, okay,
I can recognize that's coming in.
I'm gonna look at this. I can feel my emotions coming in.
I can feel potentially anger or annoyance,
but I'm gonna choose to see this objectively
and then I can properly implement a better solution
that isn't emotionally driven,
is those decisions don't usually end up good.
Yeah. Um, That's been my focus
for obviously a few days now or like a couple days,
but that's an ongoing journey.
Um, yeah. One analogy I really like is like when you
meditate, it's kinda like, uh, brooming a room.
Yes. Like you're cleaning a room
and every time a thought comes, you are trying
to take it and put it in the corner.
So at some point you're gonna be like,
you're gonna create the space between
what you're thinking and yourself.
Yes. So now it's easy to look subjectively towards this.
You know, it's really funny you bring up that analogy.
I've always, I'll probably create a video on this
for like Instagram, but I see it as like a plate, like a,
a dirty dish with a bunch of food on it.
Right. And it's like, meditation is like washing your plate,
cleaning your plate, and you have a clean plate
to like start your day.
But if you're just adding more crap
to your plate every single day, like different foods,
it's like this very toxic, very heavy thing, you know?
Um, but it's the same analogy.
It's like you get to clear hit new set Yeah. On it. Um,
I've got another nice analogy.
I love all the analogies.
This is quite relatable. Like it's, it's real life.
Um, so I think I, I a hundred percent agree,
but have you've ever gone into somebody's house?
And if there's shoes everywhere, as soon
as you walk in just scattered about all the floor,
that's where you'll put your shoes.
Mm-Hmm. But if you go in, you don't know
where they store their shoes.
Um, I dunno what it's like with different culture,
sorry, but this is how it is in England.
If, if so they're all stored in like a shoe cabinet,
you'll say, where do you, where should I put my shoes?
Mm. Because and I think that's the same in meditation.
So, um, it's easy to add mess to something
that's already messy, but if you start with fresh stuff,
you, you keep it clean
and you keep it, you keep it topped up.
But I, I, I really, I really agree with the meditation
and Wim Hof breathing.
Um, that's kind of, it's also similar to what I'm doing
with the health.
I think there was some studies on the rate of breathing kind
of affects how anxious you are to do
with your body's fight and flight system.
So if you've got really fast, rapid, shallow breathing,
then you have quite a lot of anxiety
and you're quite like, like you said, like darting about
or there's that, there's that, there's that Mm-Hmm.
But when you reset your breathing and,
and learn to breathe slowly, you're a lot more calm
and focused and can focus on the task at hand.
Yeah. Without a doubt. It's all breathing. Yeah.
It's like managing your brain
Vibration. The
vibration stuff you were talking about as well.
Sorry for interrupting. No worries.
I really, I, I agree with that
because I, I tend to get on with people
that are a bit more higher vibration
and higher energy and Exactly.
Yeah. I, I do really agree.
And I think people can tell, like when I,
when I came on the call, you, you noticed a bit
of a difference in, in myself.
Yeah. And I think when I'm just going out
and things, people just react to me in a different way
because I don't, I don't walk down like Yeah.
Looking at or acting sad.
I try and keep myself upright a bit and, and act happy.
Like I, I dunno,
I'm just really excited about life at the moment.
Love it, dude. It's law of attraction, right?
If you study law of attraction, that's what you put out is
what you get back and it's like, yeah.
Your energy, what, how you manage your
energy is what you get back.
Life is a mirror. Um, man, I I I love that.
You know, one thing that I have noticed from running this
from running ads or x
and like raising my own frequency is the type of people
who come in already have some spiritual kind
of background like context,
because you're at this frequency,
it's like you're only attracting Yeah.
Those of which are similar to you.
So it's funny, like even from clients in my agency happen
to get on a topic or something
and it's like, oh, you know, this, that,
and it's like, you only make sense, you know, it's like
back when I was, um, younger
and I didn't understand this concept.
Like I would just attract the worst of the people,
like the worst clients and the worst everything.
Um, so when you raise your own standard,
everything else raises.
But I love that you said it's easy to add mess
to something already messy.
Yeah. Honestly, I, I really like that.
Yeah. It's, it's well said.
And honestly, I'm guilty of it every day.
'cause like I keep my office really like, really clean,
but then you go into like, my bedroom
and like, there's clothes on the floor
and I'm like, I'll just add more clothes
to the floor. You know, like,
I think it's the same for me as well.
Yeah. Um, yeah.
Everything just needs a place, you know, like a system
and, um, that's awesome, dude.
Well, it sounds like you're,
you're making a lot of progress, Ethan.
I'm really excited for you. Do you guys,
do you guys have goals for 2024?
Yes. Yes, we do.
Um, that's, I, I'm, I'm working on that at the moment,
but one of my big goals is by March, well, the end of Q1,
this year I want to hit 50 k, uh, monthly revenue.
We, we spoke about that.
But I've put, I've put a date on it
and I've set a goal on it.
And at the moment I live with my parents. Mm-Hmm.
And I want to, I want to move out by, by February
and because have you also heard of this?
This is similar to what we were just speaking about,
but you are the sum
of the five people you spend the most time with.
Yep. And as horrible as it, as it sounds, my, the people,
like my parents aren't,
they're quite negative about some things.
And like, obviously I love them,
but I don't want their negativity constantly speaking
to me saying, no, you can't do this, you can't do that.
I want to be, this is also ambitious,
but I want to be a millionaire by, by at the time I'm 21.
And, and I was speaking to my mom about it last night
and she wasn't supportive
and she, I could tell she really doubted me.
Yeah. And I, I, I don't like that
because I want to just be everyone positive around me
and everyone that I kind of vibe vibrate with, kind of,
and people similar to me
that constantly raise each other up, which is,
that's also when I go to the gym, I go to the gym with Finn
and it's always a constant battle who can,
who can do more weights and who can do the most.
Yeah. We kind of raise each other up. Yeah.
And when I was speaking about Roman earlier, I have been
to the gym with just him on his own.
And he is like, oh, we'll just skip this set.
Well, oh, it doesn't matter about the weight,
so I'm not gonna try my PB today.
And I think it all kind of, all kind of relates together.
But an another thing about the law of attraction, I,
I look back on some of my past lists
and goals that I completely forget about them,
say the one I wrote last year.
And I just, by, just by the way the world works,
I just happened to achieve it.
Yep. Without a doubt. It, it,
I, I don't know how it works because I just write,
write a list that I want to achieve this
by this date, this by this date.
Yep. And then I look back at the list
and now I'm like, wow, I have actually completed all of
that, just kind
of subconsciously it just all falls into place. Yeah,
Because you wrote it down. Yeah,
Yeah. Exactly.
Without a doubt, man. It's powerful. It's very powerful.
And, um, spar, did you have anything to add to that?
I wanted to add something after.
Uh, no, you can go ahead.
So the negativity aspect, I dealt with a lot
with my parents for sure.
They were never very supportive of me being an entrepreneur.
I had the same conversations.
I wanna be, you know, millionaire, da da da, I want
to have this type of success.
You know, all they came back to me was, you know,
99% of businesses fail.
You should get a job, you should be a nurse,
you should follow all of the conventional societal things
that Filipinos do.
Um, which is not for me.
So I never, that was a big battle
for me actually for like years.
Um, until like very recently,
even though I had achieved a lot of things in my life,
it was always in the back of my mind
that like, oh, I'm not good enough.
I'm not smart enough, I'm not worthy enough.
I'm not capable of like, reaching a certain level of success
because you will, they're called abundance blocks.
And like, your limiting beliefs will only get you so far.
So all of your influences growing up, parents, friends,
teachers, maybe other like business mentors have like, kind
of like programmed you and the programmed all of us, right.
Um, society. And you'll get to a certain point
of success in your life.
Um, but in order to reach a new level of success, you have
to start examining like all
those little things about yourself.
Um, and it gets very, very, very, what's the word?
Um, nuanced. So you have these big things, right?
You do a manifestation stuff, law
of attraction, you write your goals.
Amazing. Um, now the next step is, okay,
are there any blocks in the way of that?
Do you believe that you can actually achieve that?
If you don't, if there's a little bit of a, you know,
a suggestion that maybe in your heart
or something in your throat, one of your chakras
or energy centers, like closes up, when you think of that,
it's because there's some sort of limiting belief
that's been programmed that you need to either heal
or you need to rewire.
Like you basically need to reconfigure it.
A lot of these things, um, for me, I had
done like some really deep work of meditation, of healing.
A lot of these traumas that I had with, with regards
to my parents, my dad specifically trying to like show,
like, kinda like talking down to me a lot.
Um, and it, it,
it was preventing me from really
like getting to that next level.
So whatever that is for you,
for anybody, it comes in stages.
Um, the universe will provide you what you're ready with,
but the universe will also keep showing you
what it is you need to work on internally in order
to reach that new stage.
So the same problems
that you keep arising are basically little quests,
little missions Yeah.
That are leading you toward, okay, you need to face this,
you need to deal with this to unlock the next stage.
'cause life is a video game.
And in the way that I see it right now with your
business partner or the person that you're having troubles
with, that is the next stage for you is to
assert yourself, you know, and,
and take control of your business.
And like, don't allow people to take advantage of you.
Like, that's, that's what I'm seeing from that sparse.
I feel like for you it's like balance, um, you know,
taking time versus like rushing into stuff.
Um, yeah. Take creating time and space for yourself
and like understanding that balance.
And that's what it's for me too.
It's, it's a combination of all the things for me.
Like I've done it all. So there's different levels
to it, but that's awesome.
Totally.
Yeah. I, I agree with all of it.
It's crazy. I think that's the secret to life really, is
that you're always being communicated too
based off of your reality.
And if you can observe your reality, you know, not react
to your reality and you can see, okay,
like something came up
and not like treat it with emotion as much as we tend to,
like for example, your parents, by the way,
I've studied spirituality
and all this stuff for like a few years now.
So, um, we have basically planned out all of our troubles
and cha and challenges before coming to the planet before.
'cause earth, earth is a school.
We're here to learn and grow. And so
whatever those things are, it's like we've decided
that we want to have, some people have decided
that they want to be like tortured.
They want to be this, like all these things.
And sometimes our parents are the, are the ones
that are causing the most harm and most pain for us.
But on the other side of that is the most growth, right?
Because if you can overcome that
and then share your story with other people, other people
can relate to that and heal as well.
And that is what creates a world where
more people are actually vibrating higher.
'cause it's like we're all sharing our pain
and we're all working through it together versus
creating pain in others and misleading
and, you know, controlling people.
That's like the other agenda, you know?
But it's awesome, man. You're getting there.
You're a new person, dude.
2024 is gonna be awesome year for you. I can already tell.
I I, I do believe a lot of, um, inter spirituality
and, and things like that.
Yeah. I think, I think some people just um,
like brush it off and, and disregard it.
But I think it's a bit of a, it's a mistake to do that.
'cause even if you don't believe all of it,
I think there's a lot of key learnings in there.
Oh yeah, Yeah,
Yeah. I, I've
been the, I've gone the religious route like
very long and it just wasn't adding up.
Just wasn't adding up.
And what I love about spirituality is
that it's like non-judgmental, and it's very scientific.
Like you can, you can prove
everything. You know? There's like it's
Scientific. Yeah. Yeah.
And, um, it just feels right.
You don't feel like you're being judged.
Like, at least with Christianity
and Catholicism was what I grew up with.
Like, you're a sinner.
You will go to hell, you're being punished.
Like that's all control.
You know, it's all to like, keep us minimal in our growth,
spiritual growth, like true spiritual growth.
And so for people I come across who are like not open to it
or don't really know about it, I never talk about it
because it's like, unlike people who are super religious
will like, just like shout from the
rooftops, you know what I mean?
Like, you need, you need to come
and join this 'cause it's gonna make your life better.
You're gonna get into heaven. Versus like true spiritual
people are like, I don't
talk about it unless you talk about it.
Like, it's, it's up. Yeah. It's up to you if you wanna like,
you know, 'cause it's not a cult,
you know, it's just a way of life.
Yeah. It makes sense. Makes a lot of sense.
Love it. You guys are so f*****g young, dude.
You guys have so much potential.
I'm just like so excited
for you guys. You're so f*****g young.
Holy gosh. Uh, I'm sorry,
your voice cut off.
How old are you? I'm 21.
And you're younger than me?
Yeah, I'm 18. Oh,
and, uh, you, you have an agency you said?
Yeah. Or similar? Like a bit. Oh, okay.
That's so cool though. The, at 18.
Yeah. It's wild man.
You guys are like, you guys are gifted.
You guys are really gifted, um, for your age.
Like Imma
and like, I would say like open for a lot of growth.
Uh, I know I talked about this a lot,
but like, when you're my age, you're gonna probably be like
10 steps ahead of me where I'm at right now.
Um, so that's exciting.
And I'm stoked that I'm working with people who are
that driven because you get to my age
and some people have already kind
of like worked them themselves into a job
and like, they're like cozy and complacent.
They're not really achieving.
And like your age, like, f*****g hit it hard
because so many people who are like out there like partying
or doing other wasteful things,
or like totally wasting time.
That was me. Like, if I wish,
I wish I started this s**t when I was 12.
You know? Um, yeah.
The sooner you get into it, the the faster you learn
and the faster you grow.
Uh, well, amazing, bro.
I'm gonna leave it up for like one more question, Ethan,
for you, um, before I head out,
but is there anything you wanted to ask?
Yeah. Did, would you say movement out of your
hometown slash parents' house?
Did that help you a lot?
Because I think that's the next step for me.
And I was wondering how that affected you and helped you.
Yeah, I mean, I think sparse maybe.
I mean, you, you probably get it too.
You live at home with your folks, right? Your parents.
But, uh, I was gonna add to it that, uh, I,
I keep switching between the city.
So three months I don't live here. Mm-Hmm.
Two months I come back.
But the three months that I don't live here,
I feel I'm more productive.
I'm, I feel I'm more, I don't know, uh, happier in general
with the balance of life.
Mm-Hmm. And, uh, yeah,
I think overall when, when I'm living with my parents,
it's easy for me to be more frustrated.
I don't know how to say it. It's, yeah.
Like it's e easy for me to be, you know,
I would work five days and I would get tired of it,
but if I'm living on my own, I, I can
be really more consistent, I would say.
Yeah,
Absolutely.
I think, so one of the biggest things, Ethan, um,
I think number one, having the courage
to do it is step number one, the courage to just like,
be like, Hey mom, dad, I'm, I'm doing this.
It's, they may not agree with it
and it's gonna be kind of painful,
but it's your soul wanting to grow.
Okay. I think number two, as well as it's like,
it's gonna teach you a ton of independence and autonomy
and accountability for yourself.
You're gonna realize all of the, the blessings
that you have at home, like hot meals, laundry, you know,
clean house, doing the
Dishes, Dishes, chores.
Yeah. That's gonna be on you.
So you're not, you're gonna have to learn.
That's gonna be hard if you're not already doing that.
Um, so with independence comes responsibility,
but with that responsibility comes more motivation
because you're gonna be like, oh s**t, it's just me.
I'm, no one else is gonna do it for me.
And it's going to make you better in your business
because it's gonna teach you more individual autonomous,
like independence
because you're like, oh s**t, I got bills to pay.
I have a, you know, whatever, rent your cost.
It's like, I gotta go make money, you know?
No one's gonna buy it from me. Yeah.
And I, I'm telling you right now, that is the best type
of pressure you can add to yourself to skyrocket your growth
by adding kind of like putting yourselves in situations
that are really challenging.
You find solutions,
especially if you can maintain a really positive,
appreciative attitude,
all the solutions are gonna be right there.
Um, like when I, so I was,
I realized this, uh, we had moved, uh,
to my wife's parents' house when we had our first kid just
to save money for like six months or so during Covid.
It was good up until it wasn't good
because we were living under their rules
and it was just like, dude, what the f**k?
Like, I'm, I don't wanna be here anymore.
So we ended up like, trying to find a place
and we actually found this place
and it was like, we didn't even have
to try to find this place.
It just like showed up for us.
And, uh, and when you, when you take that leap of faith,
things will fall into place.
You'll find the right people, find the perfect place.
You know what I mean? You'll get
your business started in a different way.
It's gonna be fun. I encourage it a wholeheartedly.
I'm, I'm excited for it.
Great time to be alive, dude. Yeah.
It really is So much opportunity.
I've, I really believe in that.
I mean, there's so much, if you're always looking
for the fu like looking towards the future of like,
the possibilities and like, what could be you,
you stay in this childlike kind of attitude about stuff.
It's like, that's the best place to be, you know,
not looking at the past like, oh f**k,
I wish I should've done that, or f**k this guy.
And not looking into the future of like,
oh, that's so far away.
That's so I want it now.
It's like, be excited about the future,
but be present in the moment
Yeah. As well. And
learn from the past.
I love that. Yeah. That's,
that's like, it's as simple as it gets.
Well, I'm stoked for you, Ethan.
Keep us posted on your, on your, your growth, man,
I feel like this has been cool to see you develop over,
over the, the weeks and the months.
What would you say is the biggest thing you've noticed?
Your aura, your energy is brighter.
Um, you're just resonating at a higher frequency.
So like, you know, you're smiling more,
your energy seems cleaner.
You don't feel as like heavy.
Um, and yeah, I've never seen you smile so much.
And so it's like, that's a big sign.
I can't help, I can't, I
Just f*****g wired, bro.
I just did a bunch of coke. I feel great.
I love it. I love it.
And that's the best natural energy,
natural high you can get, man. It's just,
Uh, it's not natural. John. Coke,
Coke, Coke, Coke is, damn it.
Um, awesome. Awesome.
Well guys, it was good, good connecting with you.
Thanks for jumping on today
and, uh, you gave me a lot of ideas actually for content,
Ethan, so I appreciate it.
I'm, I'm sure there's, there's many other people
who are going through what you're going through
and that gives me more ammunition
to like connect with people.
So thank you for that.
Thank you very much for the call.
Absolutely, guys. Nice. All right. Keep it up.
Thank you very much. All Right, talk soon you guys.